- 罗斯吻了我    - 不会吧
- Ross kissed me.      - No!
喔 天啊…
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
太不可思议了
It was unbelievable!
喔 天啊…
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
我们要听整个经过
We wanna hear everything.
摩妮卡 你去拿酒 把电话拔掉
Monica, get the wine and unplug the phone.
- 好   - 瑞秋
- Okay.     - Rachel.
还是我们得准备卫生纸？
Does this end well or do we need to get tissues?
- 超完美的结局   - 噢
- Oh, it ended very well.     - Oh.
等我来再开始 等我来再开始
Do not start without me! Do not start without me!
告诉我们接吻的事
Okay. All right. Let's hear about the kiss.
他是轻轻吻你的嘴唇？
Was it like a soft brush against your lips...
还是"我想立刻拥有你"那样的吻？
or was it like a, you know, "I gotta have you now" kind of thing?
刚开始真的很急迫 然后…
Well, at first it was really intense, you know? And then...
天啊 后来我们就融化在一起
Oh, God. And then we just sort of sunk into it.
好 他是抱着你的吗？还是把手放在你背后？
Oh... So, okay, was he holding you? Or were his hands on your back?
不 事实上 刚开始他手放在我腰上
No, actually, ahem, first they started out on my waist...
然后游移上来到我的头发
and then they slid up and then they were in my hair.
- 噢   - 噢
- Oh.     - Oh.
还有 呃
And, uh...
后来我吻了她
And then I kissed her.
舌吻？
Tongue?
- 没错   - 太酷了
- Yeah.     - Cool.
没有人告诉你活着有多累
∮ So no one told you life was gonna be this way ∮
上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘
∮ Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. ∮
寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累
∮ It's like you're always stuck in second gear ∮
日复一日 年复一年
∮ When it hasn't been your day, ∮
时运不济 活着受罪
∮ your week, your month, or even your year ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ but I'll be there for you ∮
纵有狂风暴雨
∮ When the rain starts to pour ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
支持一如往昔
∮ Like I've been there before ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
你我相偎相依
∮ 'Cause you're there for me too ∮
好了 看看这个坏孩子
All right, check out this bad boy!
12MB记忆体 500MB硬碟
Twelve megabytes of RAM, 500-megabyte hard drive...
可处理试算表
built-in spreadsheet capabilities...
一个每秒传输超过两万八千位元的数据机
and a modem that transmits at over 28,000 BPS.
你要拿来做什么？
Wow. What are you gonna use it for?
打电玩之类的
Games and stuff.
没工作 没有适合我的工作
There are no jobs. There are no jobs for me.
喔 等等 这里有一个
Oh, wait, here's one. Uh...
- 你可以裸体煮菜吗？ - 有人要找裸体厨师吗？
- Would you be willing to cook naked?     - There's an ad for a naked chef?
不 但如果你可以裸体煮菜 那或许就能裸体跳舞
No, but if you're willing to cook naked, then you might be willing to dance naked.
- 然后呢…   - 唔
- And then...     - Mm.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hey.
- 嘿   - 你昨晚亲热得怎么样？
- Hey.     - Oh, so how'd you make out last night?
很好笑 好笑到令人痛苦
That is funny. That is painfully funny.
不 等等
No, wait, wait.
没错 就只是令人痛苦
Yeah, that's just painful.
等等 我以为昨晚很棒
Wait a minute. I thought last night was great.
是没错 但我回到家
Yeah, it was. But I get home, okay...
看到茱莉放在我桌上的食盐水
and I see Julie's saline solution on my night table...
我就想"天啊 我是在干什么？"
and I think, "Oh, my God. What the hell am I doing?"
我跟茱莉这么棒的女人在一起
I mean, here I am with Julie, this incredible, great woman...
彼此关怀珍惜
who I care about and who cares about me...
而我就那样抛弃一切吗？
and am I just gonna throw all that away?
一瓶食盐水就给你这么大的启示？
You got all that from saline solution?
等等 我们谈的是瑞秋 你跟瑞秋的事
Wait a minute. We're talking about Rachel here. You and Rachel.
相信我 我梦想跟瑞秋在一起有十年了
Believe me, I've been dreaming about me and Rachel for 10 years.
但现在我跟茱莉在一起
But now I'm with Julie.
就是"选茱莉好 还是瑞秋？"
You know? So it's like, me and Julie, me and Rachel.
茱莉好？瑞秋好？
Me and Julie, me and Rach...
瑞秋 瑞秋
Rachel! Rachel.
- 嘿 你好   - 你好吗？
- Hey, you.     - How are you?
很好 你呢？
Good. How are you?
- 很好   - 很好
- Good. Um...     - Good.
- 嗨 亲爱的   - 嗨 茱莉 茱莉？
- Hi, honey.     - Hi, Julie. Hi, Julie?
茱莉
Julie!
你好吗？
Um, how are you?
- 很好   - 很好
- Good.     - Good.
所以大伙儿都在这儿
So everybody's here.
大伙儿都很好
Everybody's good.
你要弹点什么吗 菲比？
Were you gonna play something?
- 事实上…   - 弹吧
- Oh. Well, actually...     - Play it!
哦
Oh.
好吧
All right.
- 茱莉 我不知道你戴眼镜   - 什么？
- Julie, I didn't know you wore lenses.     - What?
嘘
Shh.
好的 各位好
Okay. Um, hi.
哈罗 各位好 可以了
Hello. Hi. Okay.
所以 恩
So, um... Ahem.
这是一首关于三角恋爱的歌
This is a song, um, about a love triangle...
发生在我虚构的三个人物之间
between three people I made up.
歌名是《其中两人昨晚接吻了》
Um, it's called, um, "Two of Them Kissed Last Night."
有个女孩名叫贝蒂
[SINGING] There was a girl We'll call her Betty
还有个叫尼尔的男孩
And a guy Let's call him Neil
我想特别郑重声明…
Now I can't stress This point too strongly
这故事不是真的
This story isn't real
现在尼尔必须决定 他要放弃哪个女孩？
Now our Neil must decide Who will be the girl that he casts aside?
是他深爱的那个贝蒂？
Will Betty be the one Who he loves truly?
还是我们叫狐狸精的那个？
Or will it be the one Who we'll call Loolie?
他必须决定 他必须决定
He must decide He must decide
虽然那是虚构故事 但他必须决定
Even though I made him up He must decide
这履历写得很好 很好 很好
Well, this is a nice résumé.
很好 很好
Nice, nice, nice.
令人印象深刻
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH THEN CHUCKLES]
莱斯特先生 这工作要做什么？广告里没说清楚
Uh, Mr. Rastatter, what does this job entail? The ad wasn't clear.
摩克力
Mockolate.
- 什么？ - 摩克力
- I'm sorry?     - Mockolate.
巧克力的人工替代品
It's a synthetic chocolate substitute.
哦
Ooh.
- 你尝一块试试   - 噢
- Well, go ahead, try a piece.     - Oh.
我们认为摩克力比巧克力更好吃
Yeah, we think that Mockolate is even better than chocolate.
- 好的   - 哈哈
- All right.     - Ha, ha.
恩
Mm.
对吧
Yeah. Ha-ha-ha.
我喜欢它碎掉的感觉
I love how it crumbles.
- 那是巧克力不会有的   - 是啊
- You see, chocolate doesn't do that.     - Ha-ha-ha. No, ma'am.
我们很快就能得到食品认证
Anyhoo, we should be getting our FDA approval any day now.
哈哈哈
Ha-ha-ha.
- 希望赶得上感恩节前上市   - 唔
- Hopefully, in time for Thanksgiving.     - Mm.
我们是这么想的 巧克力垄断了…
See, the way we look at it, chocolate dominates...
主要的年节市场 比如说复活节 圣诞节
your major food-preparation holidays. Easter, Christmas, what have you.
- 唔   - 但我们相信只要有适当行销
- Mm-hm.     - But we think given the right marketing...
我们可以让感恩节 变成摩克力的节日
we can make Thanksgiving the Mockolate holiday.
哇
Wow.
- 你不吞下去吗？ - 哈
- Aren't you gonna swallow that?     - Ha, ha.
- 我在等泡泡消失   - 噢
- Just waiting for it to stop bubbling.     - Oh.
是啊 那很棒对吧？
Yeah. Isn't that great?
- 唔   - 哈哈哈
- Mm.     - Ha-ha-ha.
这个 不管怎么 恩
Well, anyhoo, um...
总之 我们想找个能创作感恩节食谱的大厨
we're looking for chefs who can create Thanksgiving-themed recipes.
你有兴趣吗？
You interested?
当…
Abso...
然
Ahem... . Lutely!
我喜欢创作食谱 也喜欢感恩节 现在…
See, I love creating new recipes, I love Thanksgiving, and, well, now...
我还爱上摩克力
I love Mockolate.
- 真的？ - 嗯
- Really?     - Mm.
尤其是那余味 我敢说…
Especially that aftertaste. You know, I tell you...
可以撑到圣诞节
that'll last you till Christmas.
摩克力慕思如何？
How about Mockolate mousse?
感觉…
It's not...
不像感恩节
very Thanksgiving-y.
那么清教徒摩克力慕思呢？
Okay, how about Pilgrim Mockolate mousse?
跟清教徒有何关系？
What makes it Pilgrim?
我们在上面放扣环
We'll put buckles on it.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 嘿   - 罗斯有来电吗？
- Hey.     - Did Ross call?
很遗憾没有
No, I'm sorry.
他为何没打电话？
Why didn't he call?
他要跟茱莉一起 对吧？
He's gonna stay with Julie.
他会选择她而她会说
He's gonna stay with her and she'll be:
"嗨 我是茱莉 罗斯选择我
"Hi, I'm Julie. Ross picked me.
我们会结婚生子一起老死 "
We'll get married and have lots of kids and dig up stuff together!"
我无意冒犯 但听起来一点都不像她
No offense, but that sounds nothing like her.
我不知道该怎么办 我该怎么办？这真是个梦魇
I don't know what I'll do. What am I gonna do? This is like a complete nightmare!
我知道这一定很难 "不要啊 有两个女人爱我
Oh, I know. This must be so hard. "Oh, no! Two women love me!
她们两个都很漂亮又性感 我的钱包太小装不下钱
They're both gorgeous and sexy, my wallet's too small for my 50s...
我的钻石鞋也太紧了 "
and my diamond shoes are too tight!"
- 我想到了 罗斯…   - 别碰我的电脑 别碰电脑
- Hey, here's a thought, Ross...     - Don't ever touch the computer.
罗斯 你听着 我有两个字送给你
Ross, listen. I got two words for you:
三人行
Threesome.
好 我们理性一点 列张清单
Right, look. Let's get logical about this. We'll make a list.
写出瑞秋和茱莉的优缺点
"Rachel and Julie: Pros and Cons."
- 噢   - 噢
- Oh.     - Oh.
她们的名字可以用不同的字体
We'll put their names in bold with different fonts...
还能用不同颜色的栏位显示
and I can use different colors for each column.
不能用写的吗？
Can't we just use a pen?
不行 古早人
No, Amish boy.
我们先从缺点开始 那比较好玩
Let's start with the cons because they're more fun.
先说瑞秋吧
Ha-ha-ha. Rachel first.
不知道
I don't know.
我觉得…
I mean...
好吧 我想你可以说她有时候有点大小姐
All right, I guess you can say she's a little spoiled sometimes.
没有错
You could say that.
耶
Yeah.
有时候她还有点三八
I guess, you know, sometimes she's a little ditzy, you know?
有时候她也太爱漂亮了
And I've seen her be a little too into her looks.
茱莉和我有很多共同点
Uh. Oh, and Julie and I have a lot in common...
因为我们都是古生物学家
because we're both paleontologists, right?
瑞秋只是个服务生
But Rachel's just a waitress.
服务生
Waitress.
了解 你们想玩《毁灭战士》吗？
Got it. You guys wanna play "Doom"?
我们也可以继续写
Or we could keep doing this.
还有什么？
What else?
我不知道
I don't know.
喔 她的脚踝有点肉肉的
Oh, her ankles are a little chubby.
好吧 说说茱莉吧
Okay, let's do Julie.
她有何缺点？
What's wrong with her?
她不是瑞秋
She's not Rachel.
好 这是南瓜派加碎摩克力月
Okay. This is pumpkin pie with a Mockolate crust.
这是摩克力蔓越莓蛋糕 那是碎摩克力饼干
This is Mockolate cranberry cake, and these are Mockolate-chip cookies.
就像当初印地安人做的那样
Just like the Indians served.
喔 天啊
Oh, my God!
是好吃的意思吗？
"Oh, my God" good?
喔 天啊 我不敢相信你让我吃这种东西
Oh, my God! I can't believe you let me put this in my mouth.
噢 呃
Oh! Ugh!
老天爷 恶魔一定是这味道
Sweet Lord! Oh, this is what evil must taste like!
我告诉你 这东西印不出来
I'm telling you, this thing won't print.
是的 我按那按钮一百次了
Yes, I pressed that button, like, 100 times.
这是哪门子的热线电话？
You know, for a hotline, you're not so hot.
那是什么声音？
What is that in the background?
你在看《星舰迷航记》？
Are you watching Star Trek?
嘿
Hey.
你跟茱莉如何 她很伤心吗？
So how'd it go with Julie? Did you break her heart?
是啊
Yes.
真是可怕 她哭了我也哭了 她丢东西 丢到我
It was horrible. She cried, I cried. She threw things, they hit me.
唔
Mm.
我做了正确的事
I did the right thing.
史波克真的抱了他父亲？
So Spock actually hugs his father?
嘿 你们有…
Hey, do you guys have...?
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
你要去哪儿？
Where you going?
我刚回来…
I just got back from, uh...
从茱莉那儿
From Julie's.
噢
Oh.
不 不
No, no.
不是你想的那样
Uh, it's not what you think. Um...
是另一件事
It's the other thing.
什么另外的事？我想什么？
Well, heh, ahem, what's the other thing? What do I think?
这个嘛…
Well, uh...
他跟茱莉分手了
He broke up with Julie!
快去抱她 看在上天的份上
Well, go hug her, for God's sakes!
是真的？
Really?
真的
Really.
我爱的一直是你 瑞秋
It's always been you, Rach.
噢 老天
Oh, God.
噢
Oh.
喔 这太好了
Oh, this is good.
- 真是太好了   - 我知道
- This is really good.     - I know. I know.
我几乎…
It's almost...
我们去散步好吗？就我们俩 不跟他们
What do you say we go take a walk? Just us. Not them.
- 我去拿外套   - 好的 不 嘿
- Okay. Let me get my coat.     - Okay. No, hey, whoa, whoa.
我去帮你拿
I'll get your coat.
好
Okay.
他去帮我拿外套 乔伊
He's going to get my coat. He's going to get my coat, Joey!
我真不敢相信 真是太棒了
Oh, my God, you guys, I can't believe this! This is unbelievable!
- 这是什么？ - 什么？没什么
- What's that?     - What? Nothing!
- 我看到我的名字 那是什么？ - 没有…没有看到 没有看到
- What? I saw my name. What is it?     - No, no, see? See?
嘿 能列印了
Hey, it's printing!
嘿 印出来了
什么东西？让我看看
What is it? Let me see!
有人点了外套吗？
Hey, someone order a coat?
罗斯 钱德写了关于我的东西 但不让我看
Ross, Chandler wrote something about me and he won't let me see.
他不让你看？他不会让你看的
He won't? He won't!
因为那是…
Because isn't that...
你写的短篇小说？
the short story you were writing?
是的 这篇短篇小说
Yes, it is a short story...
是我写的
that I was writing.
我在里面？那让我看
And I'm in it? Well, let me read it.
不行
[IN UNISON] No!
- 拜托   - 嘿 你何不念给她听？
- Come on!     - Hey, uh, why don't you read it to her?
好吧
All right.
"那是个夏天
"It was summer.
天气很热
And it was hot.
- 瑞秋坐在那儿   - 呃？
- Rachel was there.     - Eh?
一张孤单的灰色沙发
A lonely gray couch.
尼德大叫"喔 你看"
'Oh, look! ' cried Ned.
然后他进入天国 结束"
And then the kingdom was his forever. The end!"
就这样？你只写这样？你是世界上最糟糕的作家
That's it? That's all you wrote? You're the worst writer in the world!
这不好玩
This isn't funny anymore.
那纸上一定写了我什么 我要看
There's something about me on that piece of paper, and I want to see it.
不 你不行
No, you don't.
好吧 你们要是这么幼雅的话 那就算了
All right, you know what? Fine. If you guys wanna be children, that's fine.
- 我不要看了   - 哈
- I do not need to see it!     - Ha!
不不不
No, no, no!
走吧 走!
Go, go, go!
噢
Ooh.
这是什么？
What is this?
那是…
That is...
- 不不不   - 呃
- No, no, no.     - Ah...
罗斯 这是什么？
Ross, what is this?
- 谢了   - 祝你好运
- Thank you.     - Good luck.
好吧 你只要记住 我有多爱你就行了 好吗？
Okay. Just remember how crazy I am about you, okay?
"有点三八"？
"Kind of ditzy"?
"太爱漂亮"
Ahem. "Too into her looks"?
"大小姐"？
"Spoiled"?
是"有点大小姐" 那个白痴少打了"有一点"
A little spoiled. He was supposed to type "little," the idiot!
"只是个服务生"？
"Just a waitress"?
那是…
Now, that was, uh...
我是说 相对于…
I mean, as opposed to, uh...
好吧 你饶了我吧 瑞秋？
The, um... Okay, is this over yet? Rach?
我的脚踝没有肉肉的
Ah! I do not have chubby ankles!
不 我…
No! I... No. Rach, Rach...
看另一边 看茱莉的那一栏
Okay, look at the other side. Look at Julie's column.
"她不是瑞球"？
"She's not Rachem"?
- 不…   - "瑞球"是什么东西？
- No...     - What the hell's a Rachem?
- 不   - 是古生物学家会用的蠢字眼
- No, no...     - Is that some stupid paleontology word...
而我没听过 因为我只是个服务生
that I wouldn't know because I'm just a waitress?
瑞秋 别这样
No. Rach, come on! Rach...
瑞秋…不…
Rach! Rach! No, no!
那写的是"她不是瑞秋 " 她不是…
It's "She's not Rachel"! She's not...
瑞秋？
Rachel?
（中央咖啡厅）
我的日记 太聪明了
My diary. My diary! That's brilliant!
如果我说是日记的话 她就不会要我念了
If I'd said it was my diary, she wouldn't have made me read it.
那倒是真的 你是很好的事后诸葛
No, that's true. You'd be a great person to have around the day after an emergency.
我不敢相信罗斯会列这种清单
I cannot believe Ross even made this list.
- 就是说啊   - 真是个白痴
- I know.     - What a dinkus!
别再骂他了 那是钱德的主意
Hey, cut him some slack. It was Chandler's idea.
- 什么？ - 什么？
- What?     - What?
很好 我就是在等这一刻
Oh, good. I was hoping that would come up.
- 那是你的主意？ - 你在想什么？
- This was your idea?     - What?
我们平心而论 好吗？事出必有因
Let's get some perspective here, okay? These things happen for a reason.
是啊 就是你
Yeah. You!
菲比 帮我一下 你信因果轮回之类的鬼话 不是吗？
All right, Pheebs, back me up here. You believe in that karma crap, don't you?
是啊 顺便祝你下辈子的粪金龟生活幸福
Yeah. Listen, by the way, good luck in your next life as a dung beetle.
瑞秋
Rach! Whoa...
Rach!
打开 好吗？
Hey! Uh, open up! Please?
你按铃没人应门 那就表示"滚蛋"…
When somebody does not buzz you in, Ross, that means, "Go away."
而不是"爬救生梯上来"
That doesn't mean, "Climb up the fire escape."
我要告诉你 你的优点
I just want to read you something, your "Pro List."
没兴趣
Not interested.
好…
Okay, okay.
"第一：你看益智节目时哭的模样
"Number one: The way you cry at game shows. Aw.
第二：你对朋友超好的
Number two: How much you love your friends.
第三：你紧张时玩头发的模样
Number three: The way you play with your hair when you're nervous.
第四：你能勇敢的展开新生活
Number four: How brave you are for starting your life over.
第五：你对小班超好的
Number five: How great you are with Ben.
第六：你的味道"
Number six: The way you smell."
罗斯 你在干嘛
What are you doing?
乔伊 你可以把窗打开吗？
Joey, you wanna open the window?
好啊
Oh, yeah.
- 你在外面干嘛？ - 我在…
- What are you doing out there?     - I'm, um...
你一定冻坏了 你知道你需要什么吗？
My gosh, you must be freezing. You know what you need?
来杯热腾腾的摩克力如何？
How about a nice, steaming cup of hot Mockolate?
瑞秋 拜托 请开门
Rach, come on, open up.
瑞秋 拜托 你得给我一个机会
Rach, come on. Come on. You gotta give me another chance.
不要
No.
- 不要？ - 没有错
- No?     - That's what I said.
或许我们该走了
Maybe we should go.
不 不需要 我们讲完了
No, you don't have to go. We're done talking.
我了解你一定…
Rach, come on. I know how you must...
不 你不懂 罗斯
No, you don't, Ross.
想像你自己最糟糕的缺点
Imagine the worst things you think about yourself.
你会有何感受？如果你最信任的人…
Now, how would you feel if the one person that you trusted the most in the world...
不仅把它们列出来
not only thinks them too...
还以它们做为不跟你在一起的原因
but actually uses them as reasons not to be with you.
但我想跟你在一起 尽管你有那些缺点
No, but see, I wanna be with you in spite of all those things.
你还真伟大 罗斯 我说 别走
Oh. Well, that's mighty big of you, Ross.
我说 别走
I said, don't go!
你知道吗？
You know what?
如果今天是你列单子 不管你在单子上写些什么
If things were the other way around, there is nothing you could put on a list...
都阻止不了我跟你在一起
that would ever make me not wanna be with you.
我猜那就是我们之间的差异
Well, then I guess that's the difference between us.
我是绝不会列清单的
See, I'd never make a list.
我总是不懂遇到这种情况要等多久才能开口
I never know how long you're supposed to wait in this situation before you can talk.
或许再等一会儿
Maybe a little longer.
在这些食谱当中 有些用量可能不太寻常
In some of these recipes, the quantities may seem a little unusual.
比如说椰子摩克力坚果棒
Uh, like these coconut Mockolate holiday nut bars?
我用四杯椰子粉和四杯碎坚果
I've indicated four cups of coconut and four cups of crushed nuts...
但只有一汤匙摩克力
and only one tablespoon of Mockolate.
无所谓了
Doesn't matter.
什么？
What?
我们的食品认证没有下来
Our FDA approval didn't come through.
因为白老鼠实验没过
Something about laboratory rats. Huh.
- 我很遗憾   - 是啊 不过 这是你的支票
- Oh, gosh, I'm sorry.     - Yeah. Well, anyhoo, here's your check.
感谢你这么费心准备
Thank you for all you went through.
听着 你在准备时没吃太多吧？
Um, listen, you didn't eat a lot of it while you were cooking, did you?
我是吃了一点
Well, I ate some.
喔 吃一点没关系 没有很多就好
Oh, some. That's fine. Some's not a lot.
- 哈哈哈   - 好吧
- Ha-ha-ha.     - Okay.
你尿尿时没有灼热感吧？
So it doesn't burn when you pee, does it?
哈罗
Hello.
嗨
Hi.
又是他？
Is that him again?
告诉他 我想接电话 但我的脚踝重到我走不动
Tell him I'd come to the phone, but my ankles are weighing me down.
我想这不是好时机
Listen, I don't think this is the best time.
你能为我做一件事吗？
Look, can you do something for me?
可以啊 做什么？
Sure. What?
好的
Okay.
好
All right.
听音乐好吗？
Music?
- 好啊   - 好
- Sure.     - Okay.
下一首是罗斯要献给瑞秋的歌
The next one's dedicated to Rachel from Ross.
瑞秋 他想告诉你 他深感抱歉
Rachel, he wants you to know he's sorry for what he did...
他希望你能够原谅他
and he hopes you can find it in your heart to forgive him.
∮ See the stone set in your eyes ∮
∮ See the thorn twist in your side ∮
∮ I'll wait for you ∮
∮ Sleight of hand and twist of fate ∮
∮ On a bed of nails she makes me wait ∮
∮ And I'll wait without you ∮
我们刚接到瑞秋来电
Uh, we've just gotten a call from Rachel...
她告诉我们罗斯的恶行
and she told us what Ross did.
那真是太可怕了 罗斯 如果你在听的话
It's pretty appalling. And, Ross, if you're listening...
我不想再播你的歌了
I don't wanna play your song anymore.
我们何不把时间花在有希望的情侣身上
Why don't we devote our time to a couple that stands a chance?
艾佛瑞 蜜雪儿很抱歉打了你
Avery, Michelle's sorry she hit you with her car...
她希望你们俩能够和解
and she hopes you two will work it out.
∮ There's a room where ∮
∮ I can go and ∮
∮ Tell my secrets to ∮
∮ In my room ∮
∮ In my room, in my room ∮
嗨 谢谢你再度过来
Hi. Thanks for coming in again.
不客气 我没有良心 而且我需要现金
Oh, not at all. I have no morals, and I need the cash.
我好像在照镜子
It's like I'm looking in a mirror. Ha-ha-ha.
言归正传 这东西叫开心鱼
Anyway, they're called Fish-tachios.
吃起来完全像开心果
Now, they taste exactly like pistachios...
但主要是由重组的小鱼干做的
but they're made of reconstituted fish bits.
来吧 尝尝看
Here, try one.
- 好的   - 你没对什么过敏吧？
- All right.     - You're not allergic to anything?
- 猫毛   - 喔 对不起
- Uh, cat hair.     - Oh, sorry.